National Coat & Suit Industry Recovery Board Records 5915
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Federal Trade Commission Correspondence, 1940-1943 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Federal Trade Commission, Boston to, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Federal Trade Commission, Cleveland to, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Federal Trade Commission, Saint Louis to, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Federal Trade Commission Materials from Los Angeles, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Federal Trade Commission, Philadelphia to, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Federal Trade Commission Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Federal Trade Commission Materials: Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Federal Trade Commission Correspondence and News Clippings, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Federal Trade Commission Correspondence, News Clippings, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Federal Trade Commission Correspondence, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Clippings of Articles (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Federal Trade Commission Dockets, Congressional Record (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and Draft of Questionnaire "In the Matter of Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board," docket number 4596, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board versus Federal Trade Commission, Docket 4596 (Material), 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Date may be inaccurate; listed as "1946-1945" in accession
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board versus Federal Trade Commission Docket 4596, 1947-1950 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  1947, 1950
- Documents regarding Conciliation and Arbitration; Certificate of Compliance, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Discount Investigations, 1936-1938 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Exhibits Index (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Exhibits: Correspondence Constitution and By-Laws and Collective Agreements, to, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Federal Trade Commission Exhibits Recalled (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Federal Trade Commission Exhibit Information Data (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Federal Trade Commission Exhibits Recalled (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Exhibits, Correspondence, 1935-1939 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Exhibits, Correspondence, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Exhibits, Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Fair Trade Provisions, Fair Trade Practice Violations, 1935-1948 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Fair Trade Commissions, Memorandums and Bulletins to, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Federal Trade Commission Rabiner and Jontow, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Federal Trade Commission and Traffic Committee Materials, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Investigation: Frank Gallant, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Investigation: Mayflower Coats, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Investigation: Molan Coat Company, Incorporated, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Investigation: Cohn and Plaks, Incorporated, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Investigation: William Haber, Incorporated, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Investigation: Marks and Abrahams, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Investigation: P. Moshkowsky Company Incorporated, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Investigation: Ohrbach's, 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Milton Levy Correspondence, Memorandum, etc. regarding F.T. and Fair Practice, Laws and Constitutional Amendments (Box 11, Folder 31)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board versus Federal Trade Commission Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 32)
- New York Supreme Court: Shapiro and Sons versus the Joint Board of the Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers Union, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- New York Supreme Court: Shapiro and Sons, 1933-1953 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Federal Trade Commission Pleadings: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Federal Trade Commission Docket 4596 and Report on the Coat and Suit Industry (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Federal Trade Correspondence: Report of Complaints Against the National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Report of Retail Distribution of Coats and Suits, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 38)